<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/atom.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Project Gallery</title>
  <subtitle>Documentation for using the Markata static site generator</subtitle>
  <link>https://markata.dev/</link>
  <id>https://markata.dev/project-gallery/</id>

  <link href="https://markata.dev/project-gallery/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://markata.dev/" rel="alternate" />

  <updated>2025-12-09Z</updated>

  <entry>
    <title>Markata&#39;s Docs</title>

    <id>https://markata.dev/markata-dev/</id>
    <link href="https://markata.dev/markata-dev/" rel="alternate" />

    <updated>2025-12-09Z</updated>
    <published>2025-12-09Z</published>

    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[
Markta.dev home page Markata builds it's own docs in completely in using all built in templatates and plugins. Markta.dev home page Using the plugin it is…
    ]]></summary>

    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
[![Markta.dev home page](/markata.dev_.webp)](https://markata.dev){.shadow-2xl}

Markata builds it's own docs in completely in `markata` using all built in
templatates and plugins.

[![Markta.dev home page](/markata.dev_markata_plugins_base-cli_.webp)](https://https://markata.dev/markata/plugins/base-cli/){.shadow-2xl}

Using the `markata.plugins.docs` plugin it is able to load all the python
files.  It renders out all the docstrings as markdown and shows the code in
highlighted code blocks.
    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>WaylonWalker.com</title>

    <id>https://markata.dev/waylonwalker/</id>
    <link href="https://markata.dev/waylonwalker/" rel="alternate" />

    <updated>2025-12-09Z</updated>
    <published>2025-12-09Z</published>

    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[
Waylonwalker.com home page This Waylon Walker's personal blog where he is learning in public. Posting about topics such as linux, vim, python, and kedro.…
    ]]></summary>

    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
[![Waylonwalker.com home page](/waylonwalker.com.webp)](https://waylonwalker.com)

This Waylon Walker's personal blog where he is learning in public.  Posting
about topics such as linux, vim, python, and kedro.  Flexing just a bit, after
writing content on the domain since 2017 it is achieving  15K clicks from
google every 28 days, 36 top 3 ranked keywords, and 2,400 top 10 ranked keywords.


[![Waylonwalker.com post](/waylonwalker.com_markata-configure-head.webp)](https://waylonwalker.com/markata-configure-head/)

A typical post has a header that is screenshot as the og image for display on
social platforms using selenium.  The overall theme holds similar to the home
and feeds pages.  With a large dark background image of repeating W's.


[![Waylonwalker.com feed](/waylonwalker.com_archive.webp)](https://waylonwalker.com/archive/)

Waylonwalker.com has several feeds running, but the most prominant one that is
shared in the navigation bar is the
[archive](https://waylonwalker.com/archive).  The feed itself has an RGB
backlight inspired yellow and purple glow around it.
    ]]></content>
  </entry>
</feed>
